(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D Birthday - Secret Agent Test
Wait, this is good.
I did it!
I infiltrated this place.
Success!
大成功だ！
It's a huge success!
Huh?
あ！みんなに見られた！
Ah! Everyone saw me!
うわああ！
Uwaaa!
Vestia Zeta
I can't believe you guys
were watching me this whole time! Noooo!
To be honest, um, I did feel...
I did feel eyes on me, but um,
I knew you guys were watching. It's okay.
Anyway, it's not the time to be
talking about that because today is a
special day for thee... for me! Yay!
Uh, today is... Do you know what today is?
Say it, say it! Say it, say it!
ご存じですよね？言って！
You know, don't you? Say it!
Yeah! Today is my birthday!
Happy birthday Zeta, Happy birthday Zeta,
Selamat ulang tahun, Happy birthday Zeta,
Happy birthday, Happy birthday Zeta,
Gitu gak sih lagunya? I don't know.
Is that how the song goes? I don't know.
Well...
Oh, what? You're saying something? Huh?
Mmm, nope.
Skill... skill... skill issue?
You're saying I'm a noob as a secret agent?
Bulls... okay, I can't say the rest, bulls...
Your lies, you're lying! That can't be true.
I've been working hard. I've got the stamina,
and obviously the intelligence.
IQ... IQ 200.
And strength, you know? Like the power as well.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Mmm-hmm.
So anyways, don't you worry because
I've got the perfect thing for today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Have you ever heard of a...
um... of a... of a Secret Agent School?
Yeah, so, uh, back in my days, back in my days,
I've been through hell and back.
So I invited some transfer students here
so we can prove that I'm the best secret agent,
okay?
So, um, we're gonna do some tests together
to see how tough it is to become a
professional secret agent like me, like me,
like me. I'm a good example.
Anyways, it reminds me of my, um, old
gakko-izumu, you know? Mmm.
But, to be honest, to be honest, let me...
to be honest, I don't know what we'll be
doing yet, but... ugh.
Wait, oh crap! Okay,
it's almost time for the first test!
最初のテストが... そろそろ...
The first test is... soon...
早く行かないと！
I have to go quickly!
Bye!
これな！
Check this out!
なんかさ...
You know...
あれ、ゾンビ？
Wait, a zombie?
あれ？ (威嚇の声)
Huh? (Intimidation sound)
あれ？なんか... よわの。
Huh? It's somehow... weak.
なんかみこちのカマキリの威嚇ポーズにビビってる。
It's totally scared of Mikochi's mantis intimidation pose.
ビビってる？
It's scared?
ビビってる。震えてる。
It's scared. It's shaking.
これみこちゃんわかりました。
Miko's figured it out.
なに？なに？
What? What?
コイツ、雑魚ゾンビです。
This guy is a weakling zombie.
雑魚、雑魚。
Weakling, weakling.
ざぁ〜こ。
W-e-a-k-l-i-n-g.
コイツドMかもしんない。
He might be a total masochist.
ドMゾンビ？
A masochist zombie?
ミオちゃんも行け、ミオちゃんも行け。
Mio-chan, you go too. Go, Mio-chan!
ポンコツ〜。
Useless~.
効いてる！
It's working!
あ、じゃあみこちゃんも言っていい？
Oh, then can Miko say it too?
いいよ、みこちゃんも言って。
Sure, you say it too.
ざぁ〜こ。
W-e-a-k-l-i-n-g.
効いてる、効いてる！
It's working, it's working!
珍しい！
Unbelievable!
珍しく効いてる！
It's unusually effective!
ちょっと弱々ゾンビさんなんじゃない？
Isn't he just a bit of a weakling zombie?
全然怖くないんですけど。
I'm not scared at all.
余裕かま！
Piece of cake!
うぇ〜い、余裕かま！
Yeeaah, piece of cake!
あー！みんなー！
Ah! Everyone!
お、ゼータ！
Oh, Zeta!
遅れてごめーーん！
Sorry I'm late!
ゼータ、おめでとう！
Zeta, congrats!
なにこのゾンビ？
What's with this zombie?
あれは、弱々ゾンビ！
That is a weakling zombie!
弱々ゾンビがいる。
A weakling zombie is here.
エージェントスクールの最初のテストにお招きしたけど、
We were invited for the Agent School's first test, but...
ゾンビも新入生なのかな？
I wonder if the zombie is also a new student?
えぇー？新入生？新入生なの？
What? A newcomer? Is he a newcomer?
大丈夫なの？
Is it really okay?
そうだ、でも言葉通じないけどさ、ゾンビに。
True, but we can't communicate with the zombie.
ゼータはいろんな言葉話せるよね？
Zeta, you can speak many languages, right?
ゾンビ語も喋れるんじゃないの？
Can't you speak Zombie-ish too?
ええ、ちょっと待って... 行ってきていい？
Eh, wait... Can I try talking to it?
行ってきて、行ってきて。
Go ahead, go ahead.
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
行け！
Go for it!
(ゾンビの鳴き声)
(Zombie noises)
ちょっと弱そうかも。
He looks a bit weak.
会話してる！
They're having a conversation!
あれ？
Wait?
会話してる！
They're conversing!
よし、できた。
Alright, I did it.
できた？！
You did?!
おい！ゾンビ！
Oi! Zombie!
なになに？
What's going on?
何してるの？
What are you doing?
怖がらせろって言ったでしょ？！
I told you to be scary, right?!
オリーさんだ！
It's Ollie-san!
本当に何やってたのよ！
What have you been doing?!
怒ってる、怒ってる。
She's mad, she's really mad.
ごめんね。
Apologies.
どうやら弱っちいゾンビを送っちゃったみたいね。
I probably sent over the weak zombies.
申し訳ないわね。
Sorry about that.
さて、
Anyways,
今日はみなさんにサプライズテストをご用意しました。
I called you guys here for a surprise test.
シークレットエージェントにふさわしいか、確かめてみましょう。
To see if you guys are fit to be a secret agent.
なになになにー
What what what what?
なんかわかんないけど受ける！
I don't really get it, but I'll take it!
なんかわかんないけど受けてみるか。
I don't get it either, but let's try it.
受けてみよう！
Let's try it!
さてさて、みなさん落ち着いてくださいね。
Okay, okay, calm down everyone.
では、この箱の中身を当ててもらうテストになりまーす！
In this test, you will need to guess what is inside the box!
これにはあなたたちの推理力が試されます。
This requires your investigative skills.
ラウンド1では、
For round 1,
30秒間だけ中身に触れられます。
you can feel the object for 30 seconds only.
楽しんでくださいね。
Have fun.
みなさんのリアクション、すっごく楽しみですね。
Can't wait to see your reactions.
いいリアクション期待してるよ、だって。
She says she's expecting good reactions.
完全に理解してるから。
I completely understand it.
本当だ、完全に理解してる。
True, she completely understands.
わかってるってこと？！
You mean you know?!
AZKiちゃん！
AZKi-chan!
じゃあAZKi先輩からかな？
Then is it AZKi-senpai first?
AZKiからですね！
It's from AZKi!
任せてくださいよ！
Leave it to me!
頑張って！
Good luck!
頑張れ！
これさ、みんなで協力してだよね？協力して。
This is about everyone cooperating, right? Cooperating.
そうだね、情報を集めよう。
That's right, let's gather information.
情報を集めて、伝えることに集中したいと思います。
I'll focus on gathering information and communicating it.
AZKiの挑戦
AZKi's Challenge
3, 2, 1, スタート！
3, 2, 1, start!
うわー！え？なにこれ？
Uwah! Eh? What's this?
コードのような... コード？
Something like a cord... A cord?
コード？コードのようなものではないの？
A cord? Is it not like a cord?
ちょっと待って、動いてる！
Wait a second, it's moving!
Answer: Frog toy
なに？なに？これ。
What? What? This.
なんか、ジタバタしてます、ジタバタ。
It's like, flailing around, flailing.
ジタバタ？なんか、動いてる、もしかして？
Flailing? Is it moving, maybe?
動いてるんだって！
She said it's moving!
なにこれ、怖い。
What's this, scary.
え、なんか、動いている... けど！
Eh, somehow, it's moving... but!
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
なんだ、なんだ？
What is it, what is it?
なに？なに？フォルムがわかんない。
What? What? I don't know the shape.
変な機械なんじゃない？
Isn't it some weird machine?
なんの動き？
What kind of movement?
足がバタバタしてる感じ。
It feels like legs are flapping.
大神ミオの挑戦
Ookami Mio's Challenge
じゃあミオちゃん！スタート！
Then Mio-chan! Start!
怖い、怖い、なに？なに？
Scary, scary, what? what?
は！あ！あ！
Ha! Ah! Ah!
あ、何かに気づいた。
Ah, she realized something.
でも分かったかもこれ、うちら。
But I might have figured this out, us.
わかった？！え？！
You did?! Eh?!
あー！なるほど！ハイハイハイ、ハイハイハイハイ。
Ah! I see! I get it, I get it.
あ、元気ですね。
Ah, it's energetic.
元気？元気なの？
Energetic? It's energetic?
完全に生きてます。元気、元気。
It's completely alive. Energetic, energetic.
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
あー、元気だったわ、すごい元気だった。
Ah, it was energetic, really energetic.
絶対生きてるんだ。
It's definitely alive.
ちょっと待って、待って。
Wait a second, wait.
なんか穏やかな表情。元気だったよね。
Such a peaceful expression. It was energetic, right.
さくらみこの挑戦
Sakura Miko's Challenge
ゴッドハンドみこ... やらせていただきます。
God Hand Miko... here I go!
3, 2, 1, Go!
なんかに触れた模様...
I think I touched something...
やめて! ガチですか?
Stop! Are you serious?
ガチなやつ! リアクション!
The real deal! That reaction!
わかった?
Do you know what it is?
ぜんぜんわからん。
I have no idea at all.
全然わかんない! 終わりだよ。
I have no idea! It's over!
え? ゴッドハンド?
Eh? God Hand?
ただブルってなって... めっちゃきも!
It just went 'brrr'... So gross!
じゃあ次はゼタだ! 行くぞ!
Then next is Zeta! Let's go!
ベスティア・ゼタの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
行きますよー! 3, 2, 1, スタート!
Here I go! 3, 2, 1, Start!
うわ! ほらほら!
Uwa! See, see!
これ生きてるやん!
This is alive!
待って待って待って... 生きてる気がする、ときどき。
Wait, wait, wait... I feel like it's alive sometimes.
え? なんかちゃんと触っています。
Eh? She's touching it properly.
え? 飛んでる? これ飛んでる?
Eh? Is it jumping? Is this jumping?
飛びそうではあるよね。
It does look like it's about to jump.
飛びそう? 生きてるわ!
About to jump? It's alive!
終了!
Finished!
生きてるのかな何なのかな... これちょっと...
Is it alive, or what is it... This is a bit...
でもこれみんなでね、力合わせて、誰かが当たればいいってこと。
But with everyone working together,
it's fine as long as someone gets it right.
プロペラがついたもの... みたいなのが付いてたのかなって思ったんだけど。
Something with a propeller...
I thought maybe it had something like that on it.
マジでみこ手入れた瞬間ブルってなったから、うわあってなって。
Seriously, the moment I put my hand in,
it went 'brrr', so I was like 'uwaa'.
アヒルとかの足がこうなんか、バタバタバタバタってなるのとか...
Like a duck's feet going 'flap-flap-flap-flap'...
なんかそういうおもちゃ? ミオ先輩は?
Some kind of toy like that? How about you, Mio-senpai?
これはズバリ、カエルのおもちゃです!
This is clearly a frog toy!
ぴょこぴょこぴょこってしてたってこと?
You mean it was going 'hop-hop-hop'?
ゼタちゃん、みんなのこの回答まとめを... 答えまとめてください。
Zeta-chan, the summary of everyone's answers...
please summarize the answer.
ミオ先輩の答えで! 自信満々だと思うし。
I'll go with Mio-senpai's answer! She seems very confident.
これ間違ってたらうちの全責任だ!
If this is wrong, it's all my responsibility!
カエルのおもちゃかな。
It's probably a frog toy.
解答 カエルのおもちゃ
Answer: Frog toy
あ、よくできました!
Ah, well done!
合ってる! カエルのおもちゃだ!
It's correct! It's a frog toy!
何がポイントだったんですか? 触った感じがペタペタしてて...
What was the key? It felt kind of sticky...
そのペタペタもきも... なんかね、ぴょんぴょんしてたから。
That stickiness is also gross... and because it was hopping.
ぴょんぴょんしてたから、これカエルのおもちゃっぽいなって思ったのよね。
Since it was hopping, I thought it seemed like a frog toy.
じゃあ次の問題、お願いします!
Then next question, please!
じゃあうちが行ってみますか? ゴッドハンドミオーン。
Then shall I go next? God Hand Mio-n.
大神ミオの挑戦
Ookami Mio's Challenge
スタート!
Start!
頑張れミオちゃん! なになに?
Do your best, Mio-chan! What is it?
怖い怖い! オットが怖がっている。
Scary, scary! Otto is getting scared.
嘘でしょ、なになにこれ? これは...
No way, what is this? This...
なんなんだよこれ気持ち悪い! え? え?
What the heck is this, it's gross! Eh? Eh?
気持ち悪い! 何これ何これ!
It's gross! What is this, what is this!
怖い怖い怖い! え? なに?
Scary, scary, scary! Eh? What?
わかったわかった、じゃないのその反応、そういうこと?
You know, don't you, from that reaction? Is that it?
なに? いや! いやー!
What? No! Nooo!
おおげさにやってる! 全然わかんない。
She's overreacting! I have no idea.
なんかやだ、ちょっと行ってみて行ってみて。
I don't like this, someone else go, go!
あずき行け! あずき先輩頑張れ!
AZKi, go! AZKi-senpai, do your best!
AZKiの挑戦
AZKi's Challenge
スタート!
Start!
やっぱそうだよね! 触ってみてよ。
I knew it! Try touching it.
その反応になるって! もしゃもしゃしてます。
That's exactly how you react! It's fuzzy.
ヒントは?
What's the hint?
もしゃもしゃ... え? え? なんかベタベタしてて...
Fuzzy... Eh? Eh? It's kind of sticky...
ベタベタ? え、きも! なにそれきもい。
Sticky? Eh, gross! What is that, gross.
でもこれ多分、これは何かのパーツって言われたらむずいんだけど。
But this is probably...
it's hard to say if it's a part of something.
え、なんかちょっと心にダメージ受けるよねこれ。
Eh, it's like, you take a bit of mental damage from this.
絶対行くか! 絶対行くか!
No way I'm going! No way I'm going!
ベスティア・ゼタの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
スタート! オッケー! うわー!
Start! Okay! Uwaa!
（笑い声）
あー、あー、あー！
(Laughter)
Ah, ah, ah!
初手驚くよね。
At first, you'd be surprised, right?
そう、最初は驚くんだね、これ。
Yeah, you'd be surprised at first with this.
えー？
Eh?
あー！
Ah!
あ、でも柔らかい。
Ah, but it's soft.
柔らかい、柔らかい。
It's soft, soft.
優しい。
Gentle.
優しい？優しい、柔らかい。
Gentle? Gentle and soft.
これに関してはちょっと、あのゼタの感覚が狂ってるかも。
Regarding this, my sense of touch might be broken.
何？何何？余計怖んだけど、いいの？
What? What, what? That makes it creepier. Is it okay?
いいのか、ここで？
Is it okay here?
いいのか、いいのかここで。ふむ。
Is it okay? Is it okay here? Hmm.
じゃあ、みこ先輩頑張ってね！
Well then, Miko-senpai, good luck!
あ、出た。ゴッドハンド。
Ah, it's out. God Hand.
出たゴッドハンド。いや、これ…
God Hand is out. No, this...
リアクション、リアクション来るぞー。じゃあ、
Her reaction, her reaction is coming. Well then,
さくらみこの挑戦
Sakura Miko's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
うわあああああああ！
Uwaaaaaaaaaaa!
来た、ゴッドリアクション！ゴッドリアクション来よ。
Here it comes, the god reaction! The god reaction is here.
いやあああああ！いやああああああ！
Iyaaaaaaa! Iyaaaaaaaa!
待って待って待って待って。
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
ためらっています。
She's hesitating.
手を入れることをためらっているが、
She's hesitating to put her hand in, but
ためらうよね、これ一回聞いたもん。
you'd hesitate after hearing that scream.
うぇ、うぇ、うぇ、うぇ、
Uwe, uwe, uwe, uwe,
人間じゃないか。
it's not human.
そうだよな、
Yeah, it sounds like that.
食べ物？いや、そんなことはない。
Food? No, that can't be it.
なんか起きてる、なんか起きてる！
Something's happening, something's happening!
ちょっとやばいことが起きてるじゃないか。
Something crazy is happening in there.
あの箱の中で、事件が起きている。
An incident is occurring in that box.
マスクをしてたと思うんだよね。
I thought it was a mask.
だからうちは、ピエロのマスクなんじゃないかと思いました。
So I thought it was a clown mask.
ピエロのマスク
Clown Mask
えっと、白、白塗りの女性の顔。
Um, a white, white-painted woman's face.
怖ぇよ！
Scary!
マスク？マスクか、マスクか。白塗りの女性のマスク、その答え怖ぇよ。
A mask? A mask? A white-painted woman's mask. That answer is scary!
白塗りの女性のマスク
White-Painted Woman's Mask
おそらく、YAGOOのカツラ。
Probably, YAGOO's wig.
YAGOOのカツラ
YAGOO's Wig
ええー！絶対カツラだったと思うんだよ、あれ。
Eh! I definitely think it was a wig.
ロングヘアーYAGOO。いや、ロングヘアーYAGOO。
Long hair YAGOO. Yeah, long hair YAGOO.
そうだよな、可能性、可能性高いな。
Yeah, it's possible, highly possible.
名探偵みこ先輩に信じるか、答えは、
I'll believe in Detective Miko-senpai. The answer is,
解答 ロングヘアーYAGOO！
Answer: Long Hair YAGOO!
解答 ロングヘアーYAGOO
Answer: Long Hair YAGOO
あちゃー、残念だな。
Uh-oh, too bad. That's a shame.
不正解です！
Wrong answer!
何か怖いんだけど。
Wait, something's scary.
解答 ゴーストマスク
Answer: Ghost Mask
いやあああああ！
Iyaaaaaaa!
分かってた、みこちゃん当たってるよ！当たってるよ、怖い。
I knew it! Miko-chan, you touched it! You touched it, scary.
みこちゃん当たってるよ、怖い、怖い。
Miko-chan, you touched it. Scary, scary.
当たってるの怖い。怖い怖い怖い。
It's scary that you touched it. Scary, scary, scary.
次の問題お願いします。
Next item, please.
お願いします。
Please.
じゃあ、こちらから、ゴッドハンドみこが行ってみますか。
Well then, shall God Hand Miko go first?
名探偵、名探偵決めてね、ここで。名探偵頼むよ。
Detective, Detective, decide it here. Detective, I'm counting on you.
さくらみこの挑戦
Sakura Miko's Challenge
ゴーゴーゴー！いやーだ、濡れてるって前情報で嫌だ。
Go, go, go! Nooo, I hate knowing it's wet beforehand.
うわあああああああ！
Uwaaaaaaaaaaa!
待って、待って、濡れてる！ちょっと今日一の絶叫出たけど大丈夫？
Wait, wait, it's wet! That was my loudest scream today, am I okay?
うぇ、うぇ、うぇ、うぇ、
Uwe, uwe, uwe, uwe,
何か、なんかチクチクして、ヌルヌルして。
Something's prickly and slimy.
チクチク？痛いってこと？なんかヌルヌルが濡れてて。
Prickly? Does it mean it's painful? It's slimy and wet.
濡れてる！全部に、あのトゲトゲがあります！
It's wet! There are those prickly things all over it!
全部にトゲトゲがいっぱいいる。
Prickly things all over it.
生き物？いっぱいいるって何？
A living thing? What do you mean 'there are a lot'?
どうする？AZKi先輩の方がいいかな。
What should we do? Maybe AZKi-senpai should go.
冷静な判断できるのかな、これ。
I wonder if you can make a calm judgment on this.
AZKiの挑戦
AZKi's Challenge
AZKi先輩ゴー！
AZKi-senpai, go!
え、何、あ、お、なんか濡れてる！
Eh, what, ah, oh, it's wet!
濡れてる！やっぱり濡れてるんだ。
It's wet! It really is wet.
え、なんか、湿ってる。湿ってる、湿度高め。これ。
Eh, it's kind of damp. Damp, high humidity. This.
どういうこと？え、何このトゲトゲした球体のような。
What does it mean? Eh, what is this prickly spherical thing?
球体と、その下にもトゲトゲしたものが。トゲトゲがいっぱいある。
Spherical, and there's something prickly under it too. Lots of prickly things.
痛くはないけど、トゲトゲがいっぱいある。痛くはない？
It's not painful, but there are a lot of prickly things. Not painful?
痛くはない。え、これ何だ、何なんだろう。分かんない。めっちゃムズいんだ。
It's not painful. Eh, what is this? I don't know. It's really hard.
じゃ、何だこれ！何だこれ、なんか湿ってる。
What is this! What is this? It's kind of damp.
ミオちゃんですかね、次。最後、ゼタに決めてもらって。
Mio-chan is next. Finally, Zeta will decide.
そうしよ、そうしよ。なんか嫌だな、その感想聞いた状態でやる、触るの、ちょっと嫌だ。
Let's do that. I hate touching it after hearing that impression.
大神ミオの挑戦
Ookami Mio's Challenge
ゴー！やだなぁ、濡れてるって前情報でやだ。
Go! I hate knowing it's wet beforehand.
濡れてるよ。あ、やっぱり。濡れてるなぁ。濡れてる？
It's wet. Ah, as expected. It's wet. Wet?
あ、ほんとだ、濡れてる。えー、けど、濡れてるけど、
Ah, it really is wet. Eh, but it's wet, but
なんか硬くて、たくさんいる。たくさんいるぞ、
it's kind of hard, and there are many of them. There are many,
いっぱいなんだよ。おー、これは、何だ。
there are a lot. Oh, what is this?
え、でもこれ、あんまり見かけないやつの気がする。
Eh, but I feel like it's something I don't see often.
見かけない、見かけない。はあ。
I don't see it, I don't see it. Hah.
難解だぞ...
This is hard...
おむずいんじゃない？
Isn't it really hard?
むずいな。
It's hard.
むずいんだ。
It is hard.
ゼータ！いけ！
Zeta! Go!
頑張れゼータ！
Good luck, Zeta!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
あー、オッケー、オッケー。
Ah, okay, okay.
理解はやっ！
She understands so fast!
もしかしてこれさ...
Is this perhaps...
我々はあんまり馴染みないけど...
We aren't very familiar with it, but...
ゼータは馴染みあるの？もしかして。
Are you familiar with it, Zeta? Perhaps.
これいっぱい触ったことあるかも。
I might have touched this many times.
えー！？馴染み深い。
Eh!? Familiar.
馴染み深いんだよ、ゼータにとって。
It's familiar to Zeta.
オッケー。
Okay.
我々にしたらちょっと難しいかも。
It might be a bit hard for us.
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
おそらくこれは...
Probably this is...
ウミの仲間。
Sea urchin relative.
ウニ？
Sea urchin?
苔！
Moss!
ライチ！
Lychee!
ゼータはね、たぶん、えっと、なんかインドネシア果物と近いかも。
Zeta's is, probably, um, it might be close to an Indonesian fruit.
名前はランブータン。ランブータン。
The name is Rambutan. Rambutan.
ランブータン！？
Rambutan!?
でもわかんない。ここではランブータンはいないのか。
But I don't know. Are there no Rambutan here?
自信持ってよ！ゼータが一番わかってたじゃん。
Have confidence! Zeta knew best.
答えは、せーの、ランブータン！
The answer is, one, two, Rambutan!
ピンポーンピンポーン！
Ding dong ding dong!
正解でーす！
Correct answer!
ちょっと待って。うちライチとか言ったけど全然違うわ。
Wait a minute. I said lychee but it's totally different.
ライチの味がするかも。似てる。
It might taste like lychee. It's similar.
美味しいよこれ。
This is delicious.
初めて見た。甘いの？
First time seeing it. Is it sweet?
甘い。甘っぽい。
Sweet. Sweetish.
正解の答えも不正解の答えもありましたね。
There were correct answers and incorrect answers.
でも、ゼータ、どうやらあなたの推理力はまだまだみたいだね。
But, Zeta, it seems your investigative skills aren't quite up to par yet.
もっと頑張らないと。
You need to work harder.
つまり、そう...
In other words...
スキルの問題ね！
Skill issue!
見て、スキルが問題のゼータだよ！
Look, it's the "skill issue" Zeta!
あっ、怒っちゃった！
Ah, she's getting mad!
あらあら！まったくこんなのも解けないなんて！
Oh dear! Wow, you can't even solve that!
みんなよくやったわ。
Everyone else, you did great.
次のテストも頑張ってくださいね。
Good luck on the next test.
またね！
See y'all!
ゼータも頑張ったのに。
Even though Zeta worked hard too.
さっき笑ったの？
Did you laugh earlier?
ちょっと舐めてた舐めてた。
I was looking down on it a bit.
笑ってんじゃねーよ。
Don't laugh.
笑うんじゃねえお前。
Don't you laugh.
いじめないで！かわいそう。
Don't bully him! Poor thing.
もっと床に這いつくばりなさい。
Crawl more on the floor.
ありがとうね、みんな来てくれて本当に。
Thank you everyone for coming, really.
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
あと今日は集まってくれてありがとう。
And thanks for gathering today.
次のテストの時間だから行ってくるね。
It's time for the next test so I'm going now.
行ってらっしゃい！
Take care!
ゾンビもっと祝いなさいよ。
Zombie, celebrate more.
Whoa, there's like a ring.
Wait, is this like a boxing ring?
Wait, what am I going to have to do here?
No way. Are we going to have to fight? I'm not good at fighting though.
But I mean, I can try.
Happy birthday, Zeta!
Long time no see.
This is Amelia Watson.
hololive EN's number one time-traveling detective!
How've you been?
I've been good! How are you?
Ah, glad to see you're doing well!
Yeah, I prepared the second test.
But we also have other transfer students.
Let's call them in now!
Don't let the first contestant's size fool you!
People tremble when they hear her name and her infamous line!
"Small but mighty, always rock hard, I'm rocking in!"
Please welcome... Koseki Bijou!
Koseki Bijou!
Look at her muscles, yeah!
Happy birthday Zeta!
Today I'm rock hard just for you.
Coming to the ring, she's the hero we didn't ask for,
but somehow still believe in!
She's everyone's last hope, because all the good ones were busy!
Her line is: "Meet your end, and... despair! Haiyah!"
Oh my god! Look at that walk!
IRyS!
Happy birthday Zeta!
I'm taking you down... under.
Ladies and gentlemen, hide your dumbbells and protect your ego!
Because this grim reaper doesn't just reap souls, she rips the gym apart!
Her favorite line is, "Only time can out-bench me."
Please welcome... Mori Calliope!
Oh my god, is that the secret agent Mori Calliope?
Happy birthday Zeta!
Tap out boy! Tap out boy!
Good! Everyone has gathered, right?
This is probably a big surprise, huh?
And I'm sure you're all wondering what kind of test this is gonna be!
Anyone have any guesses?
Don't say ground pounding.
Oh, correct!
We're holding a physical test using this long stick with these Bazo weights
to determine if you are fit enough to pass off as a secret agent!
Bazo! Oh my god, okay. That looks heavy.
Okay, okay. For level 1 of the physical test!
First, lift Bazo from the ring mat up to your hips as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
For level 2,
the mat will be bumpy!
You'll do the same thing as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
And for the last level,
you'll stand on the bumpy mat and balance a cup on your head!
Make sure you don't drop it, and lift Bazo up!
Well then, are you guys ready?
Let's go!
Okay, who's ready for the physical test?
Okay, maybe we should have Bijou start first?
Bijou, Bijou, go go go!
I got it!
Use your rock hard muscles to lift Bazo.
Okay, are you ready? 3, 2, 1, start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
6, 7, 8!
9, 10, 11!
12, 13, 14, 15!
16, 17, 18, 19, 20!
21!
Time's up!
21! She's rock hard! Level 1: 21.
Now IRyS! IRyS!
I got this. I'm a pro...
I'll show them my pro potential.
Start!
1, 2, 3, 4!
5, 6, 7, 8!
9, 10, 11, 12!
13, 14, 15!
16, 17, 18, 19, 20!
21!
Time's up!
IRyS, 21! It's a tie, it's a tie!
Like I said, it's more of a speed thing, isn't it?
Show us.
Ready? Start!
Start!
One! Two! Three! Four! Five!
Six! Seven! Eight! Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve! Thirteen! Fourteen! Fifteen!
Oh my god!
Sixteen! Seventeen! Eighteen! Nineteen! Twenty!
She's fast!
Twenty-one! Twenty-two! Twenty-three! Twenty-four! Twenty-five!
Twenty-six! Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight! Twenty-nine! Thirty!
Time's up!
Anyway, that was crazy! What's the score?
Twenty-nine!
Calliope Level 1: 29
Okay, now you have to show us what you're made of.
You got this! You got this, Zeta!
You ready?
Yeah.
Alright. Start!
Start!
One! Two! Three! Four! Five!
Six! Seven! Eight! Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve! Thirteen! Fourteen! Fifteen!
Sixteen! Seventeen! Eighteen! Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one! Twenty-two! Twenty-three! Twenty-four! Twenty-five!
Twenty-six! Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight! Twenty-nine! Thirty!
Time's up!
Whoa! That was awesome exercise!
I can't stand up!
You did great!
Zeta Level 1: 30
That was great.
She is a secret agent after all.
I feel like I left my body.
Okay, now who's ready for level two?
Oh, I don't know about this one...
Wait a minute, that's not fair. Those are Bijou's brothers!
Yeah, that's nasty! That's not fair!
Pebbles, I'm loving it! They're loving it!
Oh, it hurts so... okay. Start!
Start!
One! Two! Three! Four! Five!
Six! Seven! Eight! Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve! Thirteen! Fourteen! Fifteen!
Sixteen! Seventeen! Eighteen! Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one! Twenty-two! Twenty-three! Twenty-four! Twenty-five!
Twenty-six! Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight! Twenty-nine! Thirty!
Time's up!
Was that her full power?
Bijou Level 2: 34
The rocks were helping me! They gave me strength!
One's running away!
Go on, show the world again, prove to the world that you are strong.
Take your time. How does it feel?
Tell me when you're ready. Ready!
Start!
One! Two! Three! Four! Five!
Six! Seven! Eight! Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve! Thirteen! Fourteen! Fifteen!
Sixteen! Seventeen! Eighteen! Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one! Twenty-two! Twenty-three! Twenty-four! Twenty-five!
Twenty-six! Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight! Twenty-nine! Thirty!
Time's up!
IRyS Level 2: 20
She's lost for words. I think she's okay.
I'm not gonna go that hard, I'm not...
The pebbles are gonna help her out, so...
Well, I'll try to just do my best.
Tell me when you're ready. Alright, I'm good.
Start!
One! Two! Three! Four! Five!
Six! Seven! Eight! Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve! Thirteen! Fourteen! Fifteen!
Sixteen! Seventeen! Eighteen! Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one! Twenty-two! Twenty-three! Twenty-four! Twenty-five!
Twenty-six! Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight! Twenty-nine! Thirty!
Time's up!
Yogi! Yogi! Yogi!
You got more than your first time! Thirty-two!
Your form was perfect! I counted thirty-three.
It was...
The final count is 32!
Yay! I'll take it!
Step on those pebbles like they're rocks.
Bibo gives you permission.
Yeah, Bibo gives me permission.
Can I step on it?
Whoa! Oh! [Screams in pain]
She's going Super Saiyan!
Something's coming out of me!
Okay! All Zeta, are you ready?
Yeah!
Three, two, one, GO!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5... 38!
Time's up!
This is our potential level score!
I'm glad you guys are having fun!
Level 3 of the physical test is gonna be pretty tough, though.
You guys ready?
For level 3, I've got a little something behind me...
...which is a...
A cup! A cup!
Would you like a cup of tea?
Um, maybe later?
While you guys are stepping... while we are stepping...
...on the bumpy mat, we're also gonna be...
...balancing this cup on top of our head like this.
Wait, so we still have to use the mat?
Yes! It's a combination of everything.
And while lifting as well, of course.
Yeah, it doesn't affect us at all! It doesn't affect us at all!
Okay, crown the princess! Crown the princess!
There you go! It's so over! It's so over!
Bibopeople, are you ready?
Remember to use your butt and your legs. Form is important.
Okay, butt and my legs. Form.
Are you ready?
Start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5... 28!
Time's up!
Whoa! The teacup was like stuck on her head.
And then it turned over and it was hot on her head! Oh, that was so funny.
28! You got 28! Congrats!
IRyS! It's IRyS!
IRyS is princess!
I have to do this? Beautiful posture...
Exactly, yeah! Beautiful posture.
This is IRyS's strong point because she is very good at keeping it on her head.
Wait a sec, don't put it on me yet!
Okay, you may place it on my head, the crown, milady.
Here goes.
Thank you. Oh, it's beautiful. Oh, it's not too... my coronation.
Three, two, one, start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5... 10!
Time's up!
I'm proud of you.
This stupid cup! Stupid cup!
Don't blame the cup.
Maybe my good form will come in handy here.
You may place the tiara on my head.
No, you have to step on it first.
Oh, come on!
It's the pain before the game! Pain is beauty!
Maybe a wider stance is better. All right, all right, let's do it.
I shall place it on top of your crown so you have double crowns.
Okay! Are you ready, cult?
Maybe.
Three, two, one, start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Eleven!
Twelve!
Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Fifteen!
Sixteen!
Seventeen!
Eighteen!
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Twenty-two!
Twenty-three!
Twenty-four!
Twenty-five!
Yes! That's my goal! That was my goal!
Yeah, that's 24! And I didn't lose the cup even once! Sheesh!
You sure? Maybe this cup is not real?
Maybe there was tape! Maybe there was tape that helped her stay there!
No, it's not! No!
Super glue? Was it super glue on her head?
Wait, what's really going on? Let's really test it. Let's really get in there and check it out.
You're gonna use me as the test?
It's Zeta's turn!
Zeta! Zeta! Yeah!
Directly right in the center of your head, so that it's less likely to fall off.
This is like the best birthday ever!
Aw! Yay! I'm glad.
Now then, are you ready?
Three, two, one, start!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Eleven!
Twelve!
Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Fifteen!
Sixteen!
Seventeen!
Eighteen!
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Twenty-two!
Twenty-three!
Twenty-four!
Twenty-five!
Twenty-six!
You did it! 26 is the final number!
Wow! Does that mean the scores are what I think it is?
I think so!
Is anyone keeping the score?
The staff-san has been keeping score for us.
Yay, you're a winner!
I am! I am!
What are the scores again? What matters is what's inside.
Seems like you guys completed the test! Woohoo!
Some of you were able to lift pretty well. Maybe not for some, though.
It was so much fun just watching! But come on, Zeta! You're the birthday girl!
You should be showing us your crazy skills or something!
Prove it to us next test, okay?
Well then, thank you for having me!
This is Amelia Watson signing off. Until next time! Bye!
うーっし、お待たせ！ラプラス・ダークネス...
Alright, sorry to keep you waiting! Laplus Darknesss...
よし、あいつ狙おう！
Alright, let's aim for her!
やめてくれー！仲間だろー！
Stop it! We're allies, right?!
よいしょー！よいしょー！
Here we go! Heave-ho!
ダメージだー、ダメージ！
Damage! It's damage!
はい、はい、はい！楽しそう、楽しそう！
Yes, yes, yes! Looks fun, looks fun!
お、ゼータ！
Oh, Zeta!
なになに、何水鉄砲持ってるの？
Wait, why do you have a water gun too?
え、やめっ、やめて！痛い痛い痛い！
Eh, stop! Stop it! It hurts!
わー、やめてやめてやめて！
Whoa, stop it, stop it, stop it!
どういうこと？誰か説明して〜
What's going on? Someone explain!
Bokobokobo~ Kobo Kanaeru at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehe!
Zeta, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
I already told them what to do before you came here, so they know the rules!
We're gonna be testing your aim skills with this water gun!
In shooting level 1, we will see how many immobile targets you can hit within 30 seconds!
In level 2, we will see how many moving targets you can hit within 30 seconds!
And level 3 will test if you can hit the targets on the moving zombie!
Who do you think is the best shooter here?
俺だ俺だ俺だー！
It's me! Me! Me!
トワたち、みんななんとFPSやってるんでね！
Everyone here, including Towa, plays FPS games!
そうだね。
That's right.
私はやってないけどね。
I don't play them, though.
よーし！頑張るぞ！
Alright! I'll do my best!
さあ、誰が勝つんでしょうか、という感じなんですが
Well, it's like, who's going to win?
負けませんよ！
I won't lose!
私も負けないよ
I won't lose either.
Level 1
こちらに動かない的があるので、こちらをみんなで一人ずつ撃っていこうかなと思います
We have stationary targets here, so I think we'll all take turns shooting them.
頑張るー！
I'll do my best!
順番どうしましょう？
What should we do about the order?
1番！1番！やりたい！やりたい！
First! First! I want to go first!
まつりちゃんは1番、で。他の3人はね、ここら辺で見てもらいましょう
Matsuri-chan will be first. The other three, let's watch from around here.
はーい
Okay.
3, 2, 1, Start!
おお！上手！
Oh! Good!
うまい
Nice.
まつりちゃんパーフェクトおじさんじゃない？
Isn't Matsuri-chan a Perfect Old Man?
パーフェクトおじさんじゃない？
Isn't she a Perfect Old Man?
うますぎる
Too good.
やばい、うますぎる
Crazy, too good.
残り15秒！
15 seconds left!
これ、みんなにはわかんないけど、すげえムズいんだからね、これ
You guys might not know, but this is really hard.
上手、上手、上手
Good, good, good.
偏差とかもなしに
Even without lead shooting...
えっ、これ最後？
Wait, is this the last one?
えっ、パーフェクト？パーフェクト？
Wait, perfect? Perfect?
おお！まつりちゃん！
Oh! Matsuri-chan!
まつりちゃんは1発も外さず、全て取れましたー！
Matsuri-chan didn't miss a single shot and got them all!
イエーイ！
Yay!
おめでとう！すごい！
Congrats! Amazing!
すごすぎる、うますぎるよね
Too amazing, too good, right?
なんかちょっと行きづらいわ
It's a bit hard to follow that.
次、私行く
I'll go next.
お、マジ？
Oh, really?
いや、常闇様でしょ、次
No, it should be Tokoyami-sama next.
次、常闇様でしょ、リーダー！
Next is Tokoyami-sama, right, leader!
じゃあトワ
Then, Towa.
頑張れ！
Good luck!
支えるよ、支える感じ行くよ
I'll support it, I'll go with a supporting feel.
じゃあ、カウントするよ
Then, I'll count down.
3, 2, 1, Start!
おお、速い、速い
Oh, fast, fast.
速い！
Fast!
大したもんだ
Impressive.
ちょっと待って、どういうこと？
Wait a second, what's going on?
うまい、めっちゃ速い
Good, so fast.
おー、うまい
Oh, nice.
うわー、えー
Whoa, ehh.
おめでとうー！
Congrats!
だんだん超えてくんだ、これ
They keep getting better.
ああ、これは、次どうする？
Ah, this is... who's next?
いやー、先にやっとけばよかった
Man, I should have gone earlier.
じゃあ、次私やります。とりあえずね
Then, I'll go next. For now.
作戦あんだ。下半身作戦
I have a strategy. The lower body strategy.
下半身作戦
Lower Body Strategy
下半身を安定させてブレないようにする
Stabilize the lower body to prevent shaking.
下半身を安定させる
Stabilize the lower body
下半身作戦だと？
Lower body strategy, you say?
ポーズだっせぇ！
That pose is lame!
ポーズダッセェ！
Pose is lame!
ダサすぎる！
Too lame!
これでいくから
I'm going with this.
3, 2, 1, Start!
頑張れ、頑張れ！
Good luck, good luck!
頑張れー！
Good luck!
安定させて
Keep it stable.
おー、入ってる、入ってる
Oh, she's hitting, she's hitting.
いや、適当に打ってるな
No, she's just shooting blindly.
あ、でも、惜しい惜しい
Ah, but, close, close.
惜しい、惜しい
Close, close.
そらだ、そらに打ってる
It's the sky, she's shooting the sky.
もっと上、もっと上
Higher, higher.
頑張って、頑張って。今のはそらだぞ
Keep trying, keep trying. That was the sky.
あー
Ah-
Time's up!
ラプラスの結果は、まあ、ぼちぼちとなります
La+'s result is, well, so-so.
イエーイ！
Yay!
最後、行きますか
Shall we go for the last one?
行きます！頑張るー！
Let's go! I'll do my best!
ということで、じゃあ最後、ゼータ、撃ちやすく
So, finally, Zeta, to make it easier to shoot...
1秒で、1秒で
One second, one second.
いやいやいや、1秒はダメでしょ
No, no, one second is no good.
準備OK、準備OK
Ready, ready.
準備OK
Ready
3, 2, 1, Go!
頑張れ、当たった、当たった！
Good luck, it hit, it hit!
おー、すごい
Oh, amazing.
うまい！えっ、思ったより上手い
Good! Wait, she's better than I thought.
うまいよー
I'm good!
いや、これは
No, this is...
うー、あー
Ugh, ahh.
あー、全然余裕余裕
Ah, total piece of cake.
うまい！
Good!
あれ？どこだ？どこだ？
Wait, where? Where?
どこ？どこだ？
Where? Where is it?
右下、右下、ここら辺
Bottom right, bottom right, around here.
下、下、下、下、下
Bottom, bottom, bottom, bottom, bottom.
どこにある？どこだ？
Where is it? Where?
えっ、なくなった？
Wait, it's gone?
えっ、なくなった
Eh, it's gone.
いや、なに、これ？
Wait, what is this?
守護霊？これ
A guardian spirit? Is it this?
神様が手伝ってもらったのかな？
Maybe a god helped me?
おまかせ！
Leave it to me!
どこだ？あれ？
Where is it? Huh?
まつり先輩ナイスショット！
Matsuri-senpai Nice Shot!
なんかギリギリ滑り込みで、判定はClear!
Somehow, she just barely made it, result is Clear!
Clear
Level 2
あちらをご覧ください！
Please look over there!
はい！動いてる！
Yes! They're moving!
さあ、頑張っていきましょう！
Alright, let's do our best!
じゃあ、誰からいく？
So, who's going first?
俺だ、俺だ、俺だ！
Me, me, me!
私もいきたい！
I want to go too!
むずかしくなっちゃう、どんどん
It's getting harder and harder.
もう行っちゃったから、ラプラス行っちゃったからね
She's already gone, La+ has already gone out there.
いいんだ
It's fine.
やったもん勝ちでやばい
First come, first served, that's crazy.
では、いきましょう。ラプラス、いきますよ
Then, let's go. La+, here we go.
3, 2, 1, Start!
このゲームには必勝法がある
This game has a winning strategy.
This game has a winning strategy
めっちゃ回っとるやん
She's spinning so much.
うわー！
Whoa!
ねえ、これ、ずるい！
Hey, this is cheating!
うしろから撃ってるのヤバイって
Shooting from behind is crazy.
Shooting from behind is crazy
当たってないよ、当たってない
You're not hitting, you're not hitting.
当たってないよ
You're not hitting
ちゃんと見て
Look properly.
撃て！撃て！
Shoot! Shoot!
撃て撃て撃て！
Shoot, shoot, shoot!
ぐるんぐるんだからカメラ。
The camera is spinning around.
あと5秒しかないよ！
Only 5 seconds left!
一個しか倒してないよ！
You've only knocked down one!
頑張れ！頑張れ！
Go for it! Good luck!
Time's up!
あのね、すごいよ1個。
Hey, one is actually amazing.
1個ってどれ？
Which one was it?
あの後ろ向きでね。
The one that was facing backward.
ゼータいきたい？
Zeta, do you want to go?
あ、いきたい、いきたい！
Ah, I want to! I want to!
はい、じゃあゼータいきましょう。
Okay, then let's have Zeta go.
頑張れゼータくん！
Good luck, Zeta-kun!
ラプラスみたいに後ろ向かなくていい？
I don't have to face backward like La+?
うん、大丈夫。
Yeah, you're fine.
ゼータの挑戦、いきましょう！
Zeta's challenge, let's go!
3, 2, 1, Start!
Start!
頑張れ！
Good luck!
当たった！当たった！
It hit! It hit!
むず！
Hard!
もう来るからね！
It's coming already!
いやもう終わってるんだけど私が。
Wait, I'm already finished.
終わってる終わってる！ゼータもう終わってる。
She's finished, finished! Zeta is already done.
裏…裏面だったな。
The back... it was the back side.
裏面だとダメなのか。そうダメ。
Is the back side no good? Yeah, it's no good.
やばい、ゼータ後ろ！
Crap, Zeta, behind you!
これはもう後ろ、後ろしかない！
This is already just the back, only the back side!
Time's up!
ということで残念、ゼータ0枚です！
And so, unfortunately, Zeta got zero!
めちゃめちゃ難しい！これむずいよ。
This is super difficult! It's really hard.
でも惜しかったのあったね。
But there were some close ones.
裏がやばい、裏が。
The back side is the problem, the back.
裏面だったからすごい惜しい。
Since it was the back side, it was very close.
最後やから、まつりいかせてください。
Since it's the last one, please let Matsuri go.
もういっちゃった、もういっちゃった。
She's already gone, she's already gone.
まつり先輩いくぞ！
Matsuri-senpai, let's go!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
うま！マジ？
Skillful! Really?
惜しい！今のダメなんだ。
Close! That one was no good?
おお、うま！
Oh, skillful!
2個目！
Second one!
今のところ最高だよ、これ。
This is the best so far.
2個の時点でね。
With two hits already.
むずいんだからこれ。
Because this is hard.
撃ちとるうちにどんどん時間が過ぎてく！
Time keeps passing as I shoot!
これ後ろじゃない？後ろ！
Isn't this the back side? The back!
後ろはね、もうあの…
The back is already, well...
Time's up!
残念です！2個か…
Too bad! Two hits...
でも2個でもすごいよ。1だったよね？
But even two is amazing. It was one before, right?
これ気づいたぞ私。
I've realized something.
追わない方がいい。
It's better not to chase them.
絶対そう！トワも思ってた。
Definitely! Towa thought so too.
一点集中で来たところパーンのほうがいいね。
It's better to focus on one point and hit them when they come.
アドバイスを活かしてやろうかな。
I guess I'll make use of that advice.
トワ様の挑戦！ 3, 2, 1, Go!
Towa-sama's challenge! 3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
頑張れ！おおい！
Good luck! Whoa!
やばい、こっち向け！やばい！
Crap, look this way! Crap!
ええ、いくね！
Whoa, she's going for it!
裏だ！裏！
It's the back! The back!
頑張れ！
Good luck!
うお、当たった当たった当たった！
Whoa, it hit, it hit, it hit!
あと10秒！頑張れ！
10 seconds left! Good luck!
タイミングがタイミングだよ！
The timing is everything!
お、全部裏です！
Oh, they're all the back side!
まずい！
Crap!
Time's up!
難しいんだよ！2個です！
It's so hard! Two hits!
え、これクソむずい！一番でした。
Wait, this is so damn hard! That was the best one.
一緒だ、トワさん。一緒っすよ。
We're the same, Towa-san. Same score.
後ろ向いてるやつ、申し訳ないけど後ろの人と一緒。本当に。
I'm sorry, but that backward-facing one is really just like the person behind it.
Level 3
普通の的、動く的と来て、なんとこちら！ドーン！
After normal targets and moving targets, look at this! Boom!
ゾンビだ！
It's a zombie!
次はゾンビの、あの動く的になってます。
Next is this zombie-style moving target.
でも的自体は2個しかないから。
But there are only two targets on it.
こちらを狙って。なんか気持ち悪いポーズもしてますけど。
Aim for these. It's making some gross poses though.
どれどれ？トワちんからじゃあ行きましょう！
Let's see... then let's start with Towa-chin!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
はえ！うま！
Fast! Skillful!
ごめん！イージー、イージー、イージー！
Sorry! Easy, easy, easy!
え、でもなんか…おい、こっち向け！
Wait, but something... hey, look this way!
やばい！いやちょっと待って！
Crap! No, wait a minute!
え、ちょっと待って！鳥？
Wait, wait! Is that a bird?
あと一個！頭の！
One more! The one on the head!
頑張れ！代われよ！
Good luck! Change poses already!
やばいやばい！動くんだけど！
Crap, crap! It keeps moving!
いや、そ…やばいなんかポーズが！
No, it... crap, the pose!
よっしゃ、当たった！
Alright, I hit it!
Clear
ギリ！ギリクリア！すごいギリギリだった。
Barely! Barely cleared it! That was really close.
2つ取れました！ありがとうございます！
I got two! Thank you very much!
なんかゾンビだがたまに自我を持ち始めて不思議な動きをするので皆さま注意を
The zombie occasionally begins to gain a sense of self and performs mysterious movements, so everyone please be careful.
いきたい、いきたい！じゃあまつりちゃんだね。
I want to go! Okay, then it's Matsuri-chan's turn.
頑張るぞ！まつりちゃん！ 3, 2, 1, どうぞ！
I'll do my best! Matsuri-chan! 3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
はや！はや！
Fast! So fast!
ええ、はやっぷ！
Whoa, so fast!
クリア！3秒で終わりました。
Clear! I finished in 3 seconds.
Clear
3秒！3秒じゃな…
3 seconds! In just 3 seconds...
あー！
Ahhh!
ヤバいヤバい！
This is bad, this is bad!
あ、これまずい！閉じ込めてる！
Ah, this is bad! It's closing in!
これまずいよこれ！あー！やっちゃったやっちゃった！まずいよこれ！
This is bad! Ahhh! I did it, I did it! This is bad!
今まつりちゃんが3秒で打ち抜いちゃったということは...
Since Matsuri-chan just shot it down in 3 seconds...
...あの多分もう次ゾンビはこの動きしちゃいけないなっていうふうになって...
...the zombie probably realized it shouldn't move like that anymore...
えー！やばい、学習するタイプだ！
What?! Oh no, it's the type that learns!
学習しています！
It's learning!
学習ゾンビなんだ！
It's a learning zombie!
ちょっと待って、じゃあ次ラプ様？先にやる？
Wait a minute, so next is Lap-sama? Wanna go first?
先にやる？先にやる？
Wanna go first? Wanna go first?
やっぱ主役が最後でしょ！
The star should go last, after all!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
わー！あー！
Waaa! Ahhh!
当たるんかい！
You're gonna hit me?!
なんで当たんだよ！わー！
Why did it hit?! Whoa!
やばい、動きが激しいよでも！
Oh no, but the movement is so intense!
撃て撃て撃て撃て！
Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot!
撃ちなさい！
Shoot it!
おお、当たるぞ当たるぞ！
Oh, it's gonna hit, it's gonna hit!
頑張れ頑張れ、当たってるよ！
Keep going, keep going, you're hitting it!
痛い痛い！そういうゲームだっけさ？！
Ow, ow! Is that the kind of game this is?!
Time's up!
やばいちょっと途中我慢できなかった...
Oh no, I couldn't hold back halfway through...
むかつきすぎて！
Because it was so annoying!
最後の挑戦はゼータ！ 3, 2, 1, Go!
The final challenger is Zeta! 3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
わー！うわー！
Waaa! Whoa!
めっちゃ動いてる、めっちゃ動いてるよ！
It's moving a lot, it's moving a lot!
あ、当たってる当たってる、当たってるよ！
Ah, you're hitting it, you're hitting it!
めっちゃ動いてるよー！
It's moving so much!
回ってるから、めっちゃ回ってる！
It's spinning, it's spinning like crazy!
あと1枚、頑張れ！あと1枚！
One more left, go for it! Just one more!
あと1枚！当たんない！
One more! I can't hit it!
すごかった本当に！ゼータクリア！
That was amazing, really! Zeta Clear!
めちゃめちゃ軽かった、ゼータクリア！
That looked so easy, Zeta Clear!
ポイントは、2ポイントでした！わー！すごい！
The score was... 2 points! Whoa! Amazing!
みんなー！
Guys!
このテストで一番ポイントを取ったのは誰か、見てみようか？！
Should we see who got the most points in this fest?!
おー！え、めっちゃいい勝負！めっちゃいい！
Whoa! Oh, it's a really close match! Really close!
え、まつりが12点。はい。
Eh, Matsuri is 12 points. Okay.
で、トワちゃんが11点。はい。
And Towa-chan is 11 points. Okay.
で、ゼータが10点。はい。
And Zeta is 10 points. Okay.
そしてラプラスが... 14点！
And La+ is... 14 points!
4点！4点！4点！
4 points! 4 points! 4 points!
ラプラスが最下位ー！やっちゃったー！
La+ is in last place! You blew it!
1位、1位、1位の方を選んでよ！
Choose the first place, first place, first place one!
すゴーい！おめでとー！
Woooow! Congrats!
みんな本当によく頑張ったね！
You guys did very well!
でも何より、みんな楽しんでくれて嬉しかった。
And best of all, I'm glad everyone had fun.
これからもっとエイム力を上げて、こぼみたいにうまくなれるといいね。
I can't wait to see how much more you can improve your aiming skills in the future, like me.
なになに、ちょっと待って、おい、おい！
What, what, wait a minute, hey, hey!
ちょっと......こっちが喋ってるんだけど？
Um, I'm... I'm talking here.
おい！こぼの話を聞いてよ！
O! Listen to Kobo!
やばい、怒られてるよ！やばい！
Oh no, she's getting mad! Help!
ま、とにかくゼータ！
Anyway, Zeta!
シークレット・エージェントになれるまでまだまだ遠〜い道のりだよ、いい？
You still have a long, long way to go to become a full-fledged secret agent, okay?
うん、勝負しよう！
Yeah, let's have a match one day!
バーイ！またね〜
Bye! See ya~
あ、あ、まだ、まだこっちだね！
Ah, ah, wait, we're still over here!
やばい、まつりちゃんもよ、どけどけどけ！
Oh no, Matsuri-chan too, get out of the way!
今行くからね！
I'm coming now!
逃げた逃げた！えー！
She ran away, she ran away! Eh!
That was such a crazy game! I got wet!
From the water gun. They were shooting at me like crazy. I even had to change my clothes!
But, I heard there's going to be announcements today. So, are you guys ready for the announcements?
A little ad break, yes.
では、告知です！お願いします！
Now, for the announcements! Please!
じゃじゃーん！ うわ、眩しい！
Ta-da! Whoa, so bright!
She's shining so bright. Oh my God, Zeta in an angelic outfit! Isn't that so cute?
Angel costume! You guys have always said that you're scared of me, so you can't be scared of me now...
...'cause I'm the most seiso person there is! So, Seiso Zeta! Seiso Zeta is here!
どう？可愛い？可愛いでしょ？ うん、真っ白だし。
How is it? Cute? It's cute, right? Yeah, it's pure white.
The costume looks so cute, right?
Kapan lagi bisa lihat Seiso Zeta ya guys ya? Berkostum, ber-cosplay sebagai angel-angel gitu.
When else can you see Seiso Zeta, guys? Dressing up, cosplaying as an angel.
Lucu? Iya iya Zeta lucu lucu.
Cute? Yes, yes, Zeta is cute.
Aku mau! Siapa yang mau? Aku aku!
I want it! Who wants it? Me, me!
But, we don't stop here because obviously there's going to be so many more items, and we're going to introduce them now.
じゃあ、こちらをご覧ください！どうぞ！
Now, please take a look at these! Here!
じゃじゃーん！ I'm better counting but that's probably six, right? Isn't that so awesome?
Ta-da! I'm better at counting but that's probably six, right? Isn't that so awesome?
That's so cool!
So we have acrylic diorama...
...which you can put on your table. Later we'll explain.
And then we have a cap, no cap, okay?
We have a plushie nuigurumi!
And not only that, there will of course be voice...
And not only that, there will of course be voice pack...
Sorry, why did I say that? Voice...
Sorry, why did I say that? Voice pack...
There will be voice pack, and also bonus card as well!
Who wants bonus cards? Me!
So, I bet you guys are interested in this, yeah definitely.
Kalau kalian tertarik bakal ada enam item ya guys:
If you guys are interested, there will be six items:
Acrylic Diorama Set
acrylic diorama, haori, topi...
acrylic diorama, haori, cap...
...ada juga boneka...
...and a plushie...
いっぱいありますよね。うん。
There are many, right? Yeah.
Bonus card, there's also bonus card. So yeah.
Definitely we're gonna get into it, but stay, stay there.
We're not done yet. We're not done yet.
はい、次どうぞ！
Okay, next please!
アンジェリックゼータ アクリルジオラマスタンド
Angelic Zeta Acrylic Diorama Stand
Dajyaaaan! This is my acrylic diorama.
Ta-da! This is my acrylic diorama.
So cute! Arutera-mama sensei, thank you so much sensei!
あ、ママありがとう！
Ah, Mama thank you!
Mama's drawing is always so cute. かわいいでしょうね？かわいい！
Mama's drawing is always so cute. It's cute, right? So cute!
ゼータ飛んでるよ。すごくない？
Zeta is flying. Isn't it amazing?
It's super-duper cute!
I'm having an... I almost said allergic reaction.
I am having a... do you know that cuteness aggression?
Yeah, that's what I'm feeling. It's so cute! Okay!
Of course, we're gonna go to the next one. There's so much more.
じゃ、次どうぞ！
Well, next please!
ベスティア・ゼータ 羽織
Vestia Zeta Haori
Dajyaaaan! なんと、羽織！
Ta-da! What's this, a haori!
Vestia Zeta, the Vestia Zeta Haori!
I know that you guys would love to wear this at like events,
or like concerts, or maybe, you know, for future FES? Next FES?
I mean, you guys can wear it together.
You can like huddle up, wear the same haori, it would be so cute, right?
I mean, I'm wearing a uniform, so you guys can... this can be your uniform.
ライブの時とか。そう、かわいいでしょう？うん。
At times like concerts. Yes, it's cute, right? Yeah.
If everyone like uses it together, it's gonna be so cute.
Lucu banget guys, Haori.
It's so cute guys, the Haori.
Aku nggak tahu mau ngomong apa, pokoknya ini keren banget.
I don't know what to say, basically it's really cool.
Karena desainnya tuh pertama simpel.
Because the design is first of all simple.
Terus belakangnya tuh kelihatan Zeta.
Then on the back, you can see Zeta.
Terus nggak norak gitu lho guys, kayak keren aja.
And it's not tacky at all, guys, it just looks cool.
Kayak simpel, keren, cool.
Like simple, keren, and cool.
Jadi kalian juga pakainya bisa ke mana aja, nggak harus kayak konser-konser doang.
So you can wear it anywhere, not just for concerts.
You can like wear this like outside of concerts as well...
...because like it's like a sophisticated...
...because it's like a sophisticated...
...I wouldn't say elegant... it's like a cool-looking, like toned-down haori, you know?
So, befitting for me, the coolest secret agent. Okay.
Anyways, there's more! There's more! 次の！
Anyways, there's more! There's more! Next one!
だじゃあああん！
Ta-da!
「うええ」キャップ
“Uweee” Cap
Dajyaaaan! Wow! Uwe! Uwe Cap!
Ta-da! Wow! Uwe! Uwe Cap!
I almost choked on myself. It's so good!
It's a baseball cap! It's so cool!
You can use this to shield yourself from the sun, like I do, because I hate the sun.
There's like “Uweee” written on top of the cap. かわいい！ “うええ”書いてるよ。
There's like “Uweee” written on top of the cap. Cute! It says “Uweee”.
そうそうそう、ゼータのセリフ、“うええ”って書いてる。かわいいでしょう？
Yes yes, Zeta's line, “Uweee”, is written there. It's cute, right?
Of course there's like my neko... ah, not neko... my hair buns.
Kuping Zeta. There's my hair buns there and my... ribbon.
Zeta's ears. There's my hair buns there and my... ribbon.
I would call this ribbon. Ignore the whiskers, but... uh...
If you can ignore the whiskers, those are not cat whiskers, but it's cute!
You can wear it! A cap! Buy this cap, it's a good cap. No cap. Ha ha ha!
So cute! Topi ya guys! Apalagi panas-panas, harus pakai topi nggak sih guys?
So cute! It's a cap guys! Especially when it's hot, you should wear a hat, right guys?
Panas-panas, apalagi silau gitu, keren kalau pakai topi lho guys. うん。
When it's hot and bright, it looks cool to wear a hat, guys. Yeah.
Terus keren lagi hitam gitu topinya. Keren keren keren. うん。
And it's cool that the hat is black. Cool cool cool. Yeah.
まだあるのかな？うん。あると思う。うん。
Is there more? Yeah. I think there is. Yeah.
じゃ、次どうぞ！
Well, next please!
おにえむいにゃんこ ぬいぐるみ
Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie
Uuh! I... uh... it's so cute!
It's a... with the cat headband... it's called “Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie”.
おにえぬいにゃんこ ぬいぐるみ
Oni-Nui Nyanko Plushie
And it looks like a cat, I know,
but I swear it's not. Okay? It's not. It's, um...
If you notice, it's based on like Cat Day KBZ.
So it's so cute, right?
みんな、あの、Cat Dayの時覚えてる？
Everyone, um, do you remember Cat Day?
これ、This is the goods from last time.
This is... This is the goods from last time.
It's so cute, right? Look at those eyes!
Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie
It's so cute! I want to squish it...
...and just jumble it up. It's so cute!
And she's like sleeping because, um, um,
I heard that cats nap for 16 hours,
although that has nothing to do with me. I'm just saying.
It's very cute. It's like sleeping.
うーん、眠そう。眠そうゼタちゃん。
Mmm, looks sleepy. Sleepy Zeta-chan.
寝坊ゼタちゃん。可愛い！
Sleepyhead Zeta-chan. So cute!
Buy it, or else! Or else...
You don't want to miss this because everyone liked the Cat Day KBZ.
You will miss this. Okay! Even more, let's see...
Next please! 次、お願いします！
Next, please! Next, please!
ボイス
シチュエーションボイス 「運命的な出会い」
Voice
Situational Voice Pack 'A Fateful Meeting'
ボイス！ うわー、ボイス！
Voice! Wow, voice!
Voice, and it's titled "A Fateful Meeting."
Last but not least, there's also a bonus for who purchases the full set.
Okay, フルセットを買ってる人がボーナスをもらえるぞ。
Okay, people who buy the full set get a bonus.
Situational Voice Pack 'A Fateful Meeting'
Okay, okay. Kalian dapat bonus kalau kalian beli full set, oke?
Okay, okay. You get a bonus if you buy the full set, okay?
じゃあ、Last one, please! 最後、お願いします！
Then, last one, please! Last one, please!
じゃーん！ Here's the bonus!
Ta-da! Here's the bonus!
誕生日記念フルセット
Birthday Commemorative Full Set
Oh, it's the limited edition. You'll get my signature, okay?
It's so good. It's like handwritten signature and all that.
It's the best! It's limited, so get it now!
Limited, as specialized... I mean, special.
Special, mmm. Of course, um, it's a little ad break,
but we're not going to stop there because I,
even though it's my birthday, I want to give to you instead. Yeah!
Birthday Set
But it's not over yet. これで終わりじゃないよ。
But it's not over yet. It's not over with this.
It's my birthday, but I also want to give you a present as well.
So... Aren't you excited?
Okay, let's go get your present! Whoo!
Are you guys ready?
Going going my way もう放っといて 止められないね 済み任せて
Going going my way, just leave me alone. You can't stop me, so leave it to me.
凝り固まったRuleは Break it down 我慢できない Let me free
The rigid rules, break it down. I can't take it anymore, let me free.
Break It Down / Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: Ryo 'LEFTY' Miyata
目が眩んでしまいそうな イテタチのマーメイド 憧れてただけ
A mermaid in an outfit that's dazzling enough to make you dizzy. I was just longing for it.
But then 今は何にも響かない I know who I am, I
But then, now nothing resonates. I know who I am, I...
ブランディングは無関係 今は完全 無修正のナンセンス ありのままの Greedy Style
Branding is irrelevant now. It's complete uncensored nonsense. My natural greedy style.
ダサい神も興味ないの ありのままでいたいの
I'm not interested in lame gods. I want to stay as I am.
Going going my way もう放っといて 止められないね 済み任せて
Going going my way, just leave me alone. You can't stop me, so leave it to me.
凝り固まったRuleは Break it down 我慢できない Let me free
The rigid rules, break it down. I can't take it anymore, let me free.
We are special でしょ 揺るがないPride それだけでいいの
We are special, right? Unshakable pride. That's all I need.
たらればだらけのLonely Night 日々をBreak it down, break it
A lonely night full of "what-ifs." Break it down, break it, every day.
We are special でしょ 誰に言われても 私は歌うよ
We are special, right? No matter what anyone says, I will sing.
アンフェアばかりのこの世界 などBreak it down, break it down 進め
This world full of unfairness, break it down, break it down. Move forward.
Break it down, break it down 進め
Break it down, break it down. Move forward.
I just don't care about you
ハイテクなメイクやファッション 誰にもわかんないよ
High-tech makeup and fashion. No one understands.
好みと心 誰のものでもないでしょ いい加減に大人だよね
My tastes and my heart don't belong to anyone else. It's about time I grew up.
Ini Zeta apa adanya Tidak sempurna tapi sepenuhnya diriku
This is Zeta as she is. Not perfect, but completely myself.
でも今は楽しいよ ありのままでいられるから
But I'm having fun now. Because I can be myself.
Going going my way もう放っといて 止められないね 済み任せて
Going going my way, just leave me alone. You can't stop me, so leave it to me.
凝り固まったRuleは Break it down 我慢できない Let me free
The rigid rules, break it down. I can't take it anymore, let me free.
We are special でしょ 揺るがないPride それだけでいいの
We are special, right? Unshakable pride. That's all I need.
たらればだらけのLonely Night 日々をBreak it down, break it
A lonely night full of "what-ifs." Break it down, break it, every day.
We are special でしょ 誰に言われても 私は歌うよ
We are special, right? No matter what anyone says, I will sing.
あふれるバトルの世界
A world full of battles
now Break it down, Break it to smash
Can't break me down, breaking me yeah
Break it down, Break it down
Let's go, Break it down, Break it to smash
Gotta go my way ほっといて
Gotta go my way, leave me alone
止められない熱 身任せて
Surrender to the unstoppable heat
これこそがRuleは Break it down
This is the rule, break it down
我慢できない Let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free
Thank you everyone!
That was Break It Down!
Secretary, if you like it, make some noise!
Woah!
MISSION COMPLETE!
MY WORLD WOULD NOT BE COMPLETE WITHOUT U, ZE CRETARY!
YOUR SUPPORT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME! :D
LET'S KEEP DOING MISSIONS TOGETHER, FOREVER...!
KEEP BREAKIN IT DOWN!